let subtractionquestions = [
    {
        question: "What is 19 - 8",
        AnswerA: "6",
        AnswerB: "7",
        AnswerC: "8",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "9",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 - 7",
        AnswerA: "14",
        AnswerB: "15",
        AnswerC: "16",
        AnswerD: "17",
        correctAnswer: "16",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 13 - 10",
        AnswerA: "2",
        AnswerB: "3",
        AnswerC: "4",
        AnswerD: "5",
        correctAnswer: "3",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 38 - 13",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "25",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 41 - 17",
        AnswerA: "23",
        AnswerB: "24",
        AnswerC: "25",
        AnswerD: "26",
        correctAnswer: "25",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 22 - 15",
        AnswerA: "5",
        AnswerB: "6",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "7",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 37 - 11",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "26",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 26 - 8",
        AnswerA: "14",
        AnswerB: "15",
        AnswerC: "16",
        AnswerD: "17",
        correctAnswer: "16",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 38 - 19",
        AnswerA: "19",
        AnswerB: "20",
        AnswerC: "21",
        AnswerD: "22",
        correctAnswer: "19",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 25 - 17",
        AnswerA: "6",
        AnswerB: "7",
        AnswerC: "8",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "8",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 46 - 17",
        AnswerA: "26",
        AnswerB: "27",
        AnswerC: "28",
        AnswerD: "29",
        correctAnswer: "29",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 36 - 15",
        AnswerA: "21",
        AnswerB: "22",
        AnswerC: "23",
        AnswerD: "24",
        correctAnswer: "21",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 47 - 19",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "28",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 48 - 23",
        AnswerA: "15",
        AnswerB: "16",
        AnswerC: "17",
        AnswerD: "18",
        correctAnswer: "15",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 34 - 16",
        AnswerA: "15",
        AnswerB: "16",
        AnswerC: "17",
        AnswerD: "18",
        correctAnswer: "18",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 27 - 8",
        AnswerA: "19",
        AnswerB: "20",
        AnswerC: "21",
        AnswerD: "22",
        correctAnswer: "19",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 18 - 7",
        AnswerA: "9",
        AnswerB: "10",
        AnswerC: "11",
        AnswerD: "12",
        correctAnswer: "11",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 27 - 13",
        AnswerA: "13",
        AnswerB: "14",
        AnswerC: "15",
        AnswerD: "16",
        correctAnswer: "14",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 43 - 12",
        AnswerA: "28",
        AnswerB: "29",
        AnswerC: "30",
        AnswerD: "31",
        correctAnswer: "31",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 49 - 13",
        AnswerA: "35",
        AnswerB: "36",
        AnswerC: "37",
        AnswerD: "38",
        correctAnswer: "36",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 46 - 7",
        AnswerA: "38",
        AnswerB: "39",
        AnswerC: "40",
        AnswerD: "41",
        correctAnswer: "39",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 49 - 6",
        AnswerA: "42",
        AnswerB: "43",
        AnswerC: "44",
        AnswerD: "45",
        correctAnswer: "43",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 45 - 19",
        AnswerA: "23",
        AnswerB: "24",
        AnswerC: "25",
        AnswerD: "26",
        correctAnswer: "26",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 47 - 9",
        AnswerA: "35",
        AnswerB: "36",
        AnswerC: "37",
        AnswerD: "38",
        correctAnswer: "38",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 99 - 17",
        AnswerA: "79",
        AnswerB: "80",
        AnswerC: "81",
        AnswerD: "82",
        correctAnswer: "82",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 93 - 27",
        AnswerA: "63",
        AnswerB: "64",
        AnswerC: "65",
        AnswerD: "66",
        correctAnswer: "66",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 94 - 13",
        AnswerA: "81",
        AnswerB: "82",
        AnswerC: "83",
        AnswerD: "84",
        correctAnswer: "81",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 98 - 23",
        AnswerA: "74",
        AnswerB: "75",
        AnswerC: "76",
        AnswerD: "77",
        correctAnswer: "75",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 87 - 16",
        AnswerA: "71",
        AnswerB: "72",
        AnswerC: "73",
        AnswerD: "74",
        correctAnswer: "71",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 85 - 12",
        AnswerA: "73",
        AnswerB: "74",
        AnswerC: "75",
        AnswerD: "76",
        correctAnswer: "73",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 95 - 13",
        AnswerA: "80",
        AnswerB: "81",
        AnswerC: "82",
        AnswerD: "83",
        correctAnswer: "82",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 96 - 18",
        AnswerA: "75",
        AnswerB: "76",
        AnswerC: "77",
        AnswerD: "78",
        correctAnswer: "78",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 69 - 16",
        AnswerA: "51",
        AnswerB: "52",
        AnswerC: "53",
        AnswerD: "54",
        correctAnswer: "53",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 75 - 17",
        AnswerA: "56",
        AnswerB: "57",
        AnswerC: "58",
        AnswerD: "59",
        correctAnswer: "58",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 77 - 16",
        AnswerA: "61",
        AnswerB: "62",
        AnswerC: "63",
        AnswerD: "64",
        correctAnswer: "61",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 73 - 19",
        AnswerA: "53",
        AnswerB: "54",
        AnswerC: "55",
        AnswerD: "56",
        correctAnswer: "54",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 96 - 29",
        AnswerA: "67",
        AnswerB: "68",
        AnswerC: "69",
        AnswerD: "70",
        correctAnswer: "67",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 88 - 17",
        AnswerA: "64",
        AnswerB: "65",
        AnswerC: "66",
        AnswerD: "67",
        correctAnswer: "65",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 81 - 19",
        AnswerA: "61",
        AnswerB: "62",
        AnswerC: "63",
        AnswerD: "64",
        correctAnswer: "62",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 71 - 7",
        AnswerA: "64",
        AnswerB: "65",
        AnswerC: "66",
        AnswerD: "67",
        correctAnswer: "64",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 91 - 38",
        AnswerA: "51",
        AnswerB: "52",
        AnswerC: "53",
        AnswerD: "54",
        correctAnswer: "53",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 77 - 22",
        AnswerA: "52",
        AnswerB: "53",
        AnswerC: "54",
        AnswerD: "55",
        correctAnswer: "55",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 79 - 23",
        AnswerA: "53",
        AnswerB: "54",
        AnswerC: "55",
        AnswerD: "56",
        correctAnswer: "56",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 94 - 26",
        AnswerA: "65",
        AnswerB: "66",
        AnswerC: "67",
        AnswerD: "68",
        correctAnswer: "68",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 93 - 14",
        AnswerA: "76",
        AnswerB: "77",
        AnswerC: "78",
        AnswerD: "79",
        correctAnswer: "79",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 69 - 11",
        AnswerA: "56",
        AnswerB: "57",
        AnswerC: "58",
        AnswerD: "59",
        correctAnswer: "58",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 83 - 16",
        AnswerA: "65",
        AnswerB: "66",
        AnswerC: "67",
        AnswerD: "68",
        correctAnswer: "67",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 99 - 37",
        AnswerA: "61",
        AnswerB: "62",
        AnswerC: "63",
        AnswerD: "64",
        correctAnswer: "62",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 148 - 3",
        AnswerA: "142",
        AnswerB: "143",
        AnswerC: "144",
        AnswerD: "145",
        correctAnswer: "145",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 133 - 14",
        AnswerA: "117",
        AnswerB: "118",
        AnswerC: "119",
        AnswerD: "120",
        correctAnswer: "119",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 143 - 12",
        AnswerA: "121",
        AnswerB: "122",
        AnswerC: "123",
        AnswerD: "124",
        correctAnswer: "121",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 138 - 16",
        AnswerA: "120",
        AnswerB: "121",
        AnswerC: "122",
        AnswerD: "123",
        correctAnswer: "122",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 147 - 13",
        AnswerA: "133",
        AnswerB: "134",
        AnswerC: "135",
        AnswerD: "136",
        correctAnswer: "134",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 145 - 22",
        AnswerA: "122",
        AnswerB: "123",
        AnswerC: "124",
        AnswerD: "125",
        correctAnswer: "123",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 139 - 7",
        AnswerA: "130",
        AnswerB: "131",
        AnswerC: "132",
        AnswerD: "133",
        correctAnswer: "132",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 146 - 5",
        AnswerA: "141",
        AnswerB: "142",
        AnswerC: "143",
        AnswerD: "144",
        correctAnswer: "141",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 149 - 17",
        AnswerA: "130",
        AnswerB: "131",
        AnswerC: "132",
        AnswerD: "133",
        correctAnswer: "132",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 146 - 4",
        AnswerA: "142",
        AnswerB: "143",
        AnswerC: "144",
        AnswerD: "145",
        correctAnswer: "142",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 137 - 6",
        AnswerA: "131",
        AnswerB: "132",
        AnswerC: "133",
        AnswerD: "134",
        correctAnswer: "131",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 125 - 15",
        AnswerA: "107",
        AnswerB: "108",
        AnswerC: "109",
        AnswerD: "110",
        correctAnswer: "110",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 136 - 17",
        AnswerA: "116",
        AnswerB: "117",
        AnswerC: "118",
        AnswerD: "119",
        correctAnswer: "119",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 123 - 18",
        AnswerA: "105",
        AnswerB: "106",
        AnswerC: "107",
        AnswerD: "108",
        correctAnswer: "105",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 119 - 7",
        AnswerA: "111",
        AnswerB: "112",
        AnswerC: "113",
        AnswerD: "114",
        correctAnswer: "112",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 147 - 35",
        AnswerA: "112",
        AnswerB: "113",
        AnswerC: "114",
        AnswerD: "115",
        correctAnswer: "112",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 134 - 28",
        AnswerA: "104",
        AnswerB: "105",
        AnswerC: "106",
        AnswerD: "107",
        correctAnswer: "106",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 133 - 32",
        AnswerA: "100",
        AnswerB: "101",
        AnswerC: "102",
        AnswerD: "103",
        correctAnswer: "101",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 114 - 11",
        AnswerA: "102",
        AnswerB: "103",
        AnswerC: "104",
        AnswerD: "105",
        correctAnswer: "103",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 138 - 27",
        AnswerA: "108",
        AnswerB: "109",
        AnswerC: "110",
        AnswerD: "111",
        correctAnswer: "111",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 148 - 38",
        AnswerA: "110",
        AnswerB: "111",
        AnswerC: "112",
        AnswerD: "113",
        correctAnswer: "110",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 136 - 16",
        AnswerA: "117",
        AnswerB: "118",
        AnswerC: "119",
        AnswerD: "120",
        correctAnswer: "120",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 117 - 5",
        AnswerA: "112",
        AnswerB: "113",
        AnswerC: "114",
        AnswerD: "115",
        correctAnswer: "112",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 137 - 9",
        AnswerA: "125",
        AnswerB: "126",
        AnswerC: "127",
        AnswerD: "128",
        correctAnswer: "128",
    },
]